http://www.azconnector.com/privacy-policy

Arizona Connector Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Arizona Connector collects, uses, and maintains information collected from users of this Web site.
Arizona Connector is committed to respecting and protecting the privacy of visitors to our web site as well as the privacy of our customers. For visitors, we’ve structured our web site so that, in general, you can visit us on the web without identifying yourself or revealing any personal information. Arizona Connector from time to time may provide links to other sites for your convenience, however, Arizona Connector is not responsible for the information or the security of those sites.
Arizona Connector may collect information about how Users use our Web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the Web site or the domains from which Users originate. We may use “cookies” to track how Users use our Web site. A “cookie” is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site. We may also track how you were referred to our web site. For example, which search engine you used or which link you clicked on.
Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure. This privacy policy was last updated August 1, 2009.
WE STAND READY TO SOLVE YOUR INTERCONNECT PROBLEMS
